Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1102
    - Local 1102 Incoming Correspondence, October 1937 - September 5, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Emspak to Eustius Bendle Regarding Strikes, May 12, 1944; 22.
      - Emspak to Bendle Regarding Factionalism and Receivership, May 16, 1944; 23.
      - Emspak to Bendle Regarding Factionalism and Receivership, May 19, 1944; 24.
      - Emspak to Bendle Regarding Factionalism, Receivership and Strikes, May 31, 1944; 25.
    - Local 1102 Incoming Correspondence, June 27, 1945 - June 16, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Julius Emspak to John Barrett Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 27, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Barrett Regarding Bonding, July 10, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Barrett Regarding Finances, September 24, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Richard Roy Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1102 and 825, March 25, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to William Drohan Regarding Officers, April 23, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to James Click Regaridng Factionalism and UE Convention, April 10, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Roy Regarding Supplies, July 30, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Roy Regarding Factionalism and Kimmel Expulsion, August 13, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to Click Regarding Factionalism and Kimmel Expulsion, January 7, 1948; 9.
      - Emspak to John Burns Regarding General Executive Board, April 2, 1948; 10.
      - Emspak to Drohan Regarding Factionalism and Sentner Expulsion, December 28, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to Roy Regarding Singer Strike, June 24, 1949; 12.
      - Emspak to Drohan Regarding Factionalism and Sentner Expulsion, August 16, 1949; 13.
      - Emspak to Drohan Regarding Factionalism, September 27, 1949; 14.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to D.J. Kassch Regarding St. Louis Rally, November 11, 1943; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to Click Regarding Travel, November 12, 1943; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to W.W. Pierce Regarding Factionalism and Pierce Appeal, February 5, 1946; 17.
      - Fitzgerald to Louis Wagner Regarding Pierce Appeal, February 5, 1946; 18.
      - Fitzgerald to Barrett Regarding Pierce Appeal, February 5, 1946; 19.
      - Fitzgerald to Pierce Regarding General Executive Board and Pierce Appeal, February 20, 1946; 20.
      - Fitzgerald to Pierce Regarding General Executive Board and Pierce Appeal, February 27, 1946; 21.
      - Fitzgerald to Pierce Regarding General Executive Board and Pierce Appeal, May 8, 1946; 22.
      - Fitzgerald to Roy Regarding General Executive Board and Anderson Appeal, May 8, 1946; 23.
      - Fitzgerald to Pierce Regarding Pierce Appeal, May 2, 1946; 24.
      - Fitzgerald to John Burns Regarding Factionalism and Anderson Appeal, June 10, 1946; 25.
      - Fitzgerald to Burns Regarding Factionalism and Anderson Appeal, July 1, 1946; 26.
      - Fitzgerald to Burns Regarding Membership and Meeting, August 8, 1946; 27.
      - Fitzgerald to Pierce Regarding UE Convention and Pierce Appeal, October 7, 1946; 28.
      - Fitzgerald to Burns Regarding Dues and Suspension, Apirl 10, 1947; 29.
      - Fitzgerald to Burns Regarding General Executive Board, March 4, 1947; 30.
      - Fitzgerald to Burns Regarding General Executive Board, November 17, 1947; 31.
      - Fitzgerald to Roy Regarding Factionalism, April 22, 1948; 32.
      - Fitzgerald to Click Regarding General Electric and Westinghouse Negotiations, June 16, 1949; 33.
    - Local 1102 Incoming Correspondence, October 26, 1937 - January 30, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Ray Klausner to James Click Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, November 15, 1943; 1.
      - Klausner to D.J. Karsch Regarding Click Visit, December 4, 1944; 2.
      - James Matles to Peter May Regarding Finances and Headquarters, January 27y, 1938; 3.
      - Matles to Eustius Brendle Regarding Runaway Shops, March 5, 1940; 4.
      - Matles to John Burns Regarding Staff Members, December 20, 1946; 5.
      - William Mitchell to May Regarding Emerson Lawsuit, May 25, 1938; 6.
      - William Sentner to All Local Secretaries Regarding Motor Conference with Questionairre, March 1, 1940; 7.
      - Sentner to Brendle Regarding War Manpower Commission, December 30, 1942; 8.
      - Sentner to Click, November 12, 1943; 9.
      - Stuart Symington to Brendle Regarding Runaway Shops, March 1, 1940; 10.
      - A.N. Towson to Click Regarding Wages, March 22, 1944; 11.
      - Towson to Click Regarding Wages, April 4, 1944; 12.
      - Louis Wagner to Local 1102 Executive Board Regarding Factionalism, January 30, 1946; 13.
      - District President to District Board Members Regarding District Executive Board Meeting, October 26, 1937; 14.
    - Local 1102 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - John Barrett to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers and Finances, May 12, 1945; 1.
      - Barrett to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, May 19, 1945; 2.
      - Barrett to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 20, 1945; 3.
      - Barrett to Emspak Regarding Bonding, July 9, 1945; 4.
      - Barrett to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 27, 1945; 5.
      - Barrett to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, September 7, 1945; 6.
      - Barrett to Robert Logsdon Regarding Per Capita and Finances, October 22, 1945; 7.
      - Eustius Brendle to William Sentner Regarding Strikes, December 9, 1939; 8.
      - Brendle to James Byrnes Regarding Overtime, May 3, 1943; 9.
      - Brendle to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 22, 1944; 10.
      - Brendle to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, May 12, 1944; 11.
      - Brendle to Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes and Receivership, May 15, 1944; 12.
      - Brendle to Sentner Regarding Factionalism, January 2, 1946; 13.
    - Local 1102 Outgoing Correspondence, January 24, 1946 - October 1, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - John Burns to Charles Anderson Regarding Anderson Suspension, January 24, 1946; 1.
      - Burns to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Anderson Suspension, June 6, 1946; 2.
      - Burns to Fitzgerald Regarding Local Review, July 19, 1946; 3.
      - Burns to William Sentner Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, December 13, 1946; 4.
      - Burns to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism with February 17, 1947, Matles Letter to Sentner, February 3, 1947; 5.
      - Burns to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Pierce Suspension, October 29, 1947; 6.
      - Burns to Julius Emspak Regarding Factionalism, January 20, 1948; 7.
      - Burns to General Executive Board Regarding Factionalism and Polictial Action, April 23, 1948; 8.
      - Burns to Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, April 23, 1948; 9.
      - Burns to Fitzgerald Regarding Navy Factionalism, September 20, 1948; 10.
      - Burns to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Sentner Suspension, September 20, 1948; 11.
      - Burns to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Sentner Suspension, September 8, 1949; 12.
      - Burns to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Sentner Suspension, October 1, 1949; 13.
    - Local 1102 Outgoing Correspondence, June 30, 1941 - December 10, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - James Click to Julius Emspak Regarding African Americans and Strikes, June 30, 1941; 1.
      - Click to Emspak, July 1, 1941; 2.
      - Click to Emspak Regarding Dues and Check-off, March 1, 1943; 3.
      - Click to James Matles Regarding Pittsburgh Meeting, June 21, 1943; 4.
      - Click to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding New York Visit, Novmeber 13, 1943; 5.
      - Click to Emspak Regarding Overtime, November 27, 1943; 6.
      - Click to August Townsend Regarding Wages, March 17, 1944; 7.
      - Click to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Receivership, May 17, 1944; 8.
      - Click to Emspak Regarding Address, November 28, 1944; 9.
      - Click to Ray Klausner Regarding Factionalism, January 29, 1946; 10.
      - Click to Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, February 9, 1948; 11.
      - Click to William Sentner Regarding Factionalism and Sentner Suspension, December 10, 1948; 12.
      - Click to Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, June 14, 1949; 13.
      - R.H. Glasser to Emspak Regarding Officers, November 22, 1937; 14.
      - Mrs. Heffernan to James Carey Regarding Strikes, November 22, 1940; 15.
      - Alene Jones to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 6, 1937; 16.
      - Jones to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 18, 1937; 17.
      - D. Karsch to Publicity Department Regarding Publicity, March 4, 1943; 18.
      - Karsch to Fitzgerald Regarding Labor Management, November 10, 1943; 19.
      - Karsch to Emspak Regarding Labor Mangement Commiteee, November 12, 1943; 20.
      - Karsch to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 11, 1944; 21.
      - Karsch to Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes, May 20, 1944; 22.
      - Karsch to Klausner Regarding Click Trip, November 30, 1944; 23.
      - Karsch to Sentner Regarding Finances, December 26, 1944; 24.
    - Local 1102 Outgoing Correspondence, April 5, 1938 - August 23, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Louis Kimmell to Julius Emspak Regarding Stewards, April 5, 1938; 1.
      - James Liddle to William Sentner Regarding Factionalism, August 23, 1939; 2.
      - Otto Maschoff to Emspak Regarding Strikes, December 10, 1939; 3.
      - Peter May to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, June 25, 1937; 4.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Dues, July 22, 1937; 5.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, July 22, 1937; 6.
      - May to K. Ellsworth Regarding People's Press, August 10, 1937; 7.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 7, 1937; 8.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, September 10, 1937; 9.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, September 27, 1937; 10.
      - May to Emspak Regarding St. Louis Locals Meeting, October 29, 1937; 11.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, November 3, 1937; 12.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Dues, November 16, 1937; 13.
      - May to Emspak Regarding Dues, November 24, 1937; 14.
      - May to James Matles Regarding Finances and District 8, January 21, 1938; 15.
      - May to Matles Regarding Finances and District 8 Headquarters, January 21, 1938; 16.
      - May to William Mitchell Regarding Lawsuit, May 14, 1938; 17.
      - May to Emspak Regarding People's Press and Unemployment, June 22, 1938; 18.
      - Arthur Meloan to Emspak Regarding Organization, Undated; 19.
    - Local 1102 Outgoing Correspondence, January 16, 1946 - June 20, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - W.W. Pierce to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Pierce Appeal, January 16, 1946; 1.
      - Pierce to Fitzgerald Regarding Pierce Appeal, January 31, 1946; 2.
      - Pierce to General Executive Board Regarding Pierce Appeal and Factionalism, February 13, 1946; 3.
      - Pierce to Fitzgerald Regarding Pierce Appeal and Factionalism, Febraury 23, 1946; 4.
      - Pierce to Fitzgerald Regarding Pierce Appeal, May 20, 1946; 5.
      - Pierce to Julius Emspak Regarding Pierce Appeal and Factionalism, July 10, 1946; 6.
      - Pierce to UE Convention Regarding Pierce Appeal and Factionalism, August 1, 1946; 7.
      - Pierce to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, August 14, 1946; 8.
      - Pierce to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Pierce Appeal, August 15, 1946; 9.
      - Pierce to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, August 17, 1946; 10.
      - Pierce to Arthur Hepner Regarding Factionalism, August 19, 1946; 11.
      - Pierce to Fitzgerald Regarding Pierce Appeal, August 21, 1946; 12.
      - Richard Roy to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, February 22, 1946; 13.
      - Roy to General Executive Board Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 825 and 1102, March 21, 1946; 14.
      - Roy to Charles Anderson Regarding Anderson Appeal, May 1, 1946; 15.
      - Roy to Fitzgerald Regarding Anderson Appeal, May 1, 1946; 16.
      - Roy to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 9, 1947; 17-18.
      - Roy to Emspak Regarding Kimmel Suspension and Factionalism, September 10, 1947; 19.
      - Roy to Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, May 17, 1948; 20.
      - Roy to Emspak Regarding Sentner Suspension, January 14, 1949; 21.
      - Roy to Emspak Regarding Singer Strike and Factionalism, June 20, 1949; 22.
    - Local 1102 Outgoing Correspondence, October 25, 1937 - May 24, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - E.J. Stuebringer to Julius Emspak Regarding Factionalism, October 18, 1940; 1.
      - Joint Strike Commitee to James Carey Regarding Carey Visit, April 14, 1937; 2.
      - Financial Secreatary to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, October 25, 1937; 3.
      - President to Stuart Symington Regarding Wages, Negotiations and Grievances, July 7, 1939; 4.
      - Local 1102 to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, May 24, 1948; 5.
    - Local 1102 Salaray and Expense Letters, July 19 - 28, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Local 1102 Suspension and Delinquency Notices, November 1937 - June 1938 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Local 1102 Per Capita Reports, September 1937 - June 1938 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Local 1102 Financial Secretary Reports, November 1936 - July 1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Local 1102 Dues Stamps, 1936 - 1939 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Local 1102 Union Dues Reports, July 7 - September 29, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Local 1102 Newspaper, Emerson Equalizer, March 13 - March 19, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Local 1102 Newspaper, Shop Bulletin, February 15 - 17, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Local 1102 Newspaper, Local Review, June 1944 - September 1948 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Local 1102 Pamphlets, 1940, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Advanced Management Regarding Labor Relations, April 11, 1940; 1.
      - We Can Win a Wage Increase at Emerson, 1947; 2.
    - Local 1102 Leaflets, 1937 - October 13, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - William Sentner to District Executive Board Regarding Factionalism, October 20, 1937; 1.
      - "Attention Workers Mazda Lamp Plant" Regarding Organization, 1937; 2.
      - "Workers in Emerson are on the March" Regarding Organization, 1937; 3.
      - "Emerson Employees" Regarding Organization, 1937; 4.
      - "Victory for Emerson Strikers" Regarding Local 1104 Organization, 1937; 5.
      - Special Meeting Membership, March 1940; 6.
      - Local 1106 Amalgamates with Local 1102, 1940; 7.
      - Removal Notice, 1942; 8.
      - "Fall Rally" Regarding Labor Management Rally, November 1943; 9.
      - "As You Know" Regarding Anti-Communism, April 14, 1948; 10.
      - "You Stated" Regarding Sentner Expulsion and Factionalism, May 27, 1948; 11.
      - "Lay-Offs are Facing Membership" Regarding Factionalism, October 13, 1948; 12.
      - Removal Notice, 1949; 13.
      - "Communist First" Regarding Factionalism, Officers and District 8, Undated; 14.
      - "Who are Labor's Enemies" Regarding Factionalism, Officers and District 8, Undated; 15.
    - Local 1102 Newspaper Clippings, May 6, 1937 - May 23, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - "CIO Begins Drive to Unionize City's Electrical Workers", May 6, 1937; 1.
      - "Organization Drive by Electrical Union", 1937; 2.
      - "Negotiations Settles Wage Controversy at Emerson", 1939; 3.
      - "Evansville and RFC," St. Louis Star Times, February 24, 1940; 4.
      - "Emerson Union has Plan to Keep Company in City", March 2, 1940; 5.
      - "Union O-Kays Plan for Employees to Aid Emerson Co.", March 6, 1940; 6.
      - "Two Electrical Union Locals to Seek Wage Rise," St. Louis Post, October 19, 1946; 7.
      - "Union Heads Raps Attacks of CIO Communist Here", August 15, 1946; 8.
      - "Communist Aid Suspended by Electrical Union", August 12, 1947; 9.
      - "United Electrical Worker Members to Vote on Plan to Oust Sentner", January 14, 1948; 10.
      - "Anti-Red Local Again Defiant of UEW Leaders", January 17, 1948; 11.
      - "No Motion Made to Oust Senter" with "Store Union Here Votes to Withdraw from International" Article and William Sentner Letter to James Matles, January 1948; 12.
      - "Sentner Ouster Expected to Aid Non-Reds in UE," St. Louis Post, May 23, 1948; 13.
    - Local 1102 Photo Mock Up, Undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Local 1102 Shark Industry Organization, September 9 - 29, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - A. Meloan to Local 301, September 9, 1937; 1.
      - William Turnbill to James Matles, September 20, 1937; 2.
      - Matles to Meloan, September 29, 1937; 3.
    - Local 1102 Defense Job Training, August 22 - 27, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - F.M. Karches to James Carey with Newspaper Clipping, August 22, 1940; 1.
      - Carey to Karches, August 27, 1940; 2.
    - Local 1102 Mailing List, October 18, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, October 18, 1940; 1.
      - Emspak to Sentner, October 18, 1940; 2.
    - Local 1102 Evansville Relocation, March 7 - 14, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Letter to James Carey with Memo and William Sentner Letter to James Matles, March 7, 1940; 1.
      - Proposal to Emerson Electric Manufacturing Company, 1940; 2.
      - Matles to W.S. Symington, March 11, 1940; 3.
      - Carey to Symington, March 12, 1940; 4.
      - Stuart Symington to Matles, March 14, 1940; 5.
    - Local 1102 Symington Book Loan, September 16 - October 16, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Stuart Symington to James Carey, September 16, 1940; 1.
      - Symington to Carey, September 27, 1940; 2.
      - Secretary of Carey to Symington, October 4, 1940; 3.
      - Symington to Carey, October 16, 1940; 4.
    - Local 1102 Click Draft Deferment, Septmeber 16, 1941 - January 27, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - William Symington to Local Draft Board, September 16, 1941; 1.
      - James Click to Draft Board Appeals, January 14, 1942; 2.
      - Morris Levin to Albert Fitzgerald, January 17, 1942; 3.
      - Fitzgerald to Levin, January 27, 1942; 4.
      - Eustius Brendle Letter, Undated; 5.
    - Local 1102 Gun Turrent Wages, March 22, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - A.N. Towsen to Henry Fiering, March 22, 1944; 1.
      - Towsen to Joe Marty, March 22, 1944; 2.
    - Local 1102 Per Capita Arrears, October 23 - 24, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Robert Logsdon to Julius Emspak, October 23, 1945; 1.
      - Logsdon to Emspak, October 24, 1945; 2.
    - Local 1102 Pierce Appeal, April 1945 - September 1946 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Union Brief, March 1, 1945; 1.
      - District Appeals Committee Ruling, April 1945; 2.
      - Louis Wagner to James Click, May 10, 1945; 3.
      - O.J. Spreitler Statement, February 20, 1946; 4.
      - Sam Russo Statement, February 26, 1946; 5.
      - J.C. McCreary Statement, February 26, 1946; 6.
      - James Meyer Statement, February 26, 1946; 7.
      - William Pierce to General Executive Board, March 4, 1946; 8.
      - Pierce Statement, March 30, 1946; 9-11.
      - Pierce Answer to Brendle Brief, March 1946; 12.
      - William Sentner to Ernest DeMaio, June 12, 1946; 13.
      - DeMaio to Sentner, June 12, 1946; 14.
      - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald, August 15, 1946; 15.
      - Pierce Speech, August 16, 1946; 16.
      - Appeals Commitee Recommendations, September 1946; 17.
      - Convention Proceedings Excerpt, September 9, 1946; 18.
      - Appeal Memo, September 1946; 19.
      - James McKnight Statement, 1946; 20.
      - Joe Stein Minutes, Undated; 21.
      - Memo, Undated; 22.
      - General Executive Board Excerpt, Undated; 23.
    - Local 1102 Constituion Changes, February 25 - 27, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - R.J. Bergman to Albert Fitzgerald, February 25, 1946; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Bergman, February 27, 1946; 2.
    - Local 1102 Anderson Suspension, May 27, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - Charles Anderson to Richard Roy, May 27, 1946; 1.
      - Anderson to Albert Fitzgerald, May 27, 1946; 2.
    - Local 1102 Kimmel Suspension, May 23 - August 4, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Appeal Committee Findings, May 23, 1947; 1.
      - Louis Kimmell to Julius Emspak, August 4, 1947; 2.
      - Kimmell to W.K. Cuthbert, September 4, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, October 31, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, October 31, 1947; 5.
      - DeMaio to Emspak, November 5, 1947; 6.
      - Joseph Pogue to Emspak, December 8, 1947; 7.
      - Robert Logsdon to James Click with Newspaper Clippings, January 15, 1948; 8.
      - William Sentner to Emspak, January 19, 1948; 9.
    - Local 1102 Factionalism, January 29, 1947 - July 16, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Robert Logsdon to All District 8 Unions, January 29, 1947; 1.
      - Dottie Aukamp to Jim Click, Februray 12, 1947; 2.
      - Memo Regarding Special Local Meeting, April 11, 1947; 3.
      - James Matles to Logsdon, October 22, 1947; 4.
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, November 14, 1947; 5.
      - Resolution, April 1948; 6.
      - Sentner to District Executive Board Memebers with Notice, Leaflets and July 16, 1948, Sentner Letter to John Burns, July 20, 1948; 7.
    - Local 1102 Opal Cline and Helen Sage Case, April 23 - October 18, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - William Sentner to Officers and Stewards, April 23, 1948; 1.
      - Opal Cline Letter, September 30, 1948; 2.
      - Sentner to E.H. Fair, October 5, 1948; 3.
      - Report on Hearing Before Industrial Employment Review Board, October 11, 1948; 4.
      - Helen Sage Statement, October 11, 1948; 5.
      - Cline to Evansville Courier, October 15, 1948; 6.
      - Sentner to All Local 1102 Memebers, October 18, 1948; 7.
    - Local 1102 Negotiations and Factionalism, February 10 - June 1948 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - James Matles to William Sentner, February 19, 1948; 1.
      - Sentner to Matles, February 10, 1948; 2.
      - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald, May 19, 1948; 3.
      - Ernest DeMaio to Oscar Scmidt, May 25, 1948; 4.
      - Sentner to Ray Klausner, May 26, 1948; 5.
      - Klausner to Sentner, May 26, 1948; 6.
      - DeMaio to Schmitt, June 1948; 7.
    - Local 1102 Sentner Suspension, January 21, 1948 - October 1949 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - Secretary of Julius Emspak to William Sentner, January 21, 1948; 1.
      - Sentner to Joseph Pogue, May 27, 1948; 2.
      - Appeals Committee Findings, July 24, 1948; 3.
      - Sentner to Emspak, August 10, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Sentner, August 27, 1948; 5.
      - Robert Logsdon to Emspak, August 30, 1948; 6.
      - Chronology, August 1949; 7.
      - Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, September 27, 1949; 8.
      - Emspak to John Gojack with Emspak Letter to William Drohan, September 27, 1949; 9.
      - Notice, September 28, 1949; 10.
      - DeMaio to Emspak, October 5, 1949; 11.
      - Report of General Executive Board Sub-Committee with Statement of Local Executive Board, October 1949; 12.
      - DeMaio to Emspak, October 5, 1949; 13.
      - Memo, October 1949; 14.
    - Local 1102 Correspondence, April 19, 1937 - February 17, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Local 1102-Emerson Conference, April 19, 1937; 1.
      - Henry Fiering to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change, February 1938; 2.
      - William Sentner to James Matles Regarding Organization and Women with June 18, 1939, St. Louis Locals Executive Board Minutes and Leaflets, July 5, 1939; 3.
      - Check-off Card with John Driy Letter to Emerson Employees, November 10, 1939; 4.
      - F.W. Jessop to William Symington Regarding Prices, February 29, 1940; 5.
      - W. Symington to James Carey Regarding Unemployment, May 28, 1940; 6.
      - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1102 and 1104, October 15, 1940; 7.
      - W. Symington to Carey Regarding UE News, November 18, 1940; 8.
      - Stuart Symington to Carey Regarding Publicity, November 22, 1940; 9.
      - Suggested Standards for Apprenticeships, February 1941; 10.
      - Charles Anderson to Sentner Regarding Finances, February 17, 1943; 11.